The Walt Hawver Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 12. News Consultants, 12; Boxes: 7 - 8 274 - 349
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: July 1966 (Folder 314, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Oct. 1966 (Folder 315, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Nov. 1966 (Folder 316, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Feb. - Mar. (Folder 317, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: July 1967 (Folder 318, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Oct. 1967 (Folder 319, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Nov. 1967 (Folder 320, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Oct. 1968 (Folder 321, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Nov. 1968 (Folder 322, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Feb. - May (Folder 323, Box 7)
  - ARB Television Audience Estimates Albany-Schenectady-Troy: Nov. (Folder 324, Box 7)
  - ARB Television Audience Estimates Albany-Schenectady-Troy: Feb.- (Folder 325, Box 7)
  - ARB Television Audience Estimates Houston: May 1971 (Folder 326, Box 7)
  - Arbitron Television Audience Estimates in the Houston Market: Nov. (Folder 327, Box 8)
  - Arbitron Television Audience Estimates in the Houston Market: Jan. (Folder 328, Box 8)
  - Arbitron Television Audience Estimates in the Houston Market: May (Folder 329, Box 8)
  - American Research Bureau Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience (Folder 330, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Essential Findings and Recommendations (Folder 331, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Viewer Attitudes Toward Houston Television (Folder 332, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Essential Findings and Recommendations (Folder 333, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Viewer Attitudes Toward Houston Television (Folder 334, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Essential Findings and Recommendations (Folder 335, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Viewer Attitudes Toward Houston Television (Folder 336, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Essential Findings and Recommendations (Folder 337, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Viewer Attitudes Toward Houston Television (Folder 338, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Television Trends 1977 (Folder 339, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Essential Findings and Recommendations (Folder 340, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Viewer Attitudes Toward Houston Television (Folder 341, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Summary of Essential Findings and (Folder 342, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Viewer Attitudes Toward Houston Television (Folder 343, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Summary and Recommendations Houston (Folder 344, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Summary of Essential Findings and (Folder 345, Box 8)
  - McHugh and Hoffman, Inc. Survey of Viewer Attitudes Toward (Folder 346, Box 8)
  - Memos on Consultants (Folder 347, Box 8)
  - New York State Associated Press Broadcasters’ Association awards (Folder 348, Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 349, Box 8)
- 13. KTRK Memorandums, 1970 - 1981; 13; 9 350 - 356
  Series contains memos sent to and by KTRK from 1970 through 1981.
  - KTRK memos 1970- 1978 (1 of 4) (Folder 350, Box 9)
  - KTRK memos 1970- 1978 (2 of 4) (Folder 351, Box 9)
  - KTRK memos 1970- 1978 (3 of 4) (Folder 352, Box 9)
  - KTRK memos 1970- 1978 (4 of 4) (Folder 353, Box 9)
  - KTRK memos 1978- 1979 (Folder 354, Box 9)
  - KTRK memos 1980- 1981 (1 of 2) (Folder 355, Box 9)
  - KTRK memos 1980- 1981 (2 of 2) (Folder 356, Box 9)
- 14. Reports, Interview Transcripts and photographs: CCB leadership, 14; 9 357 - 375
  Series contains Reports, Interview Transcripts and Photographs that pertain to Capital Cities executives
  - Daniel B. Burke (Folder 357, Box 9)
  - Thomas S. Murphy (Folder 358, Box 9)
  - Burke/Murphy post 1986 (1 of 2) (Folder 359, Box 9)
  - Burke/Murphy post 1986 (2 of 2) (Folder 360, Box 9)
  - Frank Stanton (Folder 361, Box 9)
  - Warren Buffett (Folder 362, Box 9)
  - Joe Dougherty (Folder 363, Box 9)
  - Frank Smith (Folder 364, Box 9)
  - Lowell Thomas (Folder 365, Box 9)
  - Bill Casey (Folder 366, Box 9)
  - Ruth Fitzgerald (Folder 367, Box 9)
  - Don Pels (Folder 368, Box 9)
  - Gerald Dickler (Folder 369, Box 9)
  - Joel Rosenbloom and Roger Wollenburg (Folder 370, Box 9)
  - Ron Doerfler (Folder 371, Box 9)
  - Philip Meek (Folder 372, Box 9)
  - Robert Ballow (Folder 373, Box 9)
  - John Sias (Folder 374, Box 9)
  - Photographs of the annual CCB management meeting: 1985 and 1995 (Folder 375, Box 9)
- 15. Interviews on audio cassette representing all phases of the Capital Cities experience, 1954 - 1994; 15; Boxes: 10 - 11 376 - 505
  Series contains audio cassette tapes containing interviews from nearly one hundred sources about their experiences with Capital Cities.
  - Partial Index of Tapes compiled by Walt Hawver (Folder 376, Box 10)
  - Adkins, Luther: executive Vice President- Fort Worth Star-Telegram / Joseph Donth - Star- Telegram 6/3/86 (Folder Item 377, Box 10)
  - Appleton, Richard: price comm. Executive VP-ex KFSN-WPVI-WTVD (Folder Item 378, Box 10)
  - Arcara, Jim: ABC/Cap Cities radio stations 3/1/90 (Folder Item 379, Box 10)
  - Arcara, Jim: CCB radio11/8/90 (Folder Item 380, Box 10)
  - Arcara, Jim: executive VP radio- Cap Cities (Folder Item 381, Box 10)
  - Ballow, Robert: labor attorney Cap Cities 7/31/86 (Folder Item 382, Box 10)
  - Berkley, Gary: Bellview, Ill 1/29/91 (Folder Item 383, Box 10)
  - Beuth, Philip: WKBW- TV Buffalo, NY 1 of 3 (Folder Item 384, Box 10)
  - Beuth, Philip: WKBW- TV Buffalo, NY 2 of 3 (Folder Item 385, Box 10)
  - Beuth, Philip: WKBW- TV Buffalo, NY 3 of 3 (Folder Item 386, Box 10)
  - Beuth, Philip: 9/14/88: re: Fresno / Lois Rasmussen KFSN (Folder Item 387, Box 10)
  - Bibb, Dick: Fort Worth Star-Telegram 6/3/86 and Jerry Flemmons: author “Amon” 6/3/86 (Folder Item 388, Box 10)
  - Blockus, Ray: ed. Page and Tom Bigler: columnist 6/10/86 (Folder Item 389, Box 10)
  - Bradley, Charles: WPVI openings 3/13/86 (Folder Item 390, Box 10)
  - Buffet, Warren: on Thomas Murphy NAB 4/91 (Folder Item 391, Box 10)
  - Buffet, Warren: Berkshire Hanthaway, Omaha Nebraska 6/16/86 (Folder Item 392, Box 10)
  - Buffet, Warren: at CCB management meeting (Folder Item 393, Box 10)
  - Bures, Paul and Ernie Greup (informal) (Folder Item 394, Box 10)
  - Bures, Paul: re: minorities- Durham- reading (off speed) 4/15/88 (Folder Item 395, Box 10)
  - Bures, Paul: general manager WTVD, g.s.m. KTRK 7/25/85 (Folder Item 396, Box 10)
  - Burg, George: Assistant to the publisher Kansas City Star-Times 5/20/86 (Folder Item 397, Box 10)
  - Burke, Dan: president and CEO Cap Cities 7/15/85 (Folder Item 398, Box 10)
  - Burke, Dan: 6/30/92 (main tape) (Folder Item 399, Box 10)
  - Burke, Dan: CCB Managers Meeting Phoenix Comments (Folder Item 400, Box 10)
  - Burke, Dan: final, Phoenix 2/10/94 (Folder Item 401, Box 10)
  - Butler, Jack: retired executive editor Fort Worth Star-Telegram 6/2/86 (Folder Item 402, Box 10)
  - Coady, Michael: Sr. VP- Fairchild 7/29/86 (Folder Item 403, Box 10)
  - Collins, Gene: operations manager, WTEN-TV Albany, NY. 1955-70 (Folder Item 404, Box 10)
  - Condon, Joe: 40 years of WROW-AM-FM, Albany (Folder Item 405, Box 10)
  - Connor, Richard: publisher, times-herald 6/11/86 (Folder Item 406, Box 10)
  - Cushman, Glen: Oregon News Papers 1/5/91 (Folder Item 407, Box 10)
  - Daniels, Aaron: pres. ABC radio nets 12/13/90 (Folder Item 408, Box 10)
  - Dickler, Gerry: NY 9/88 (Folder Item 409, Box 10)
  - Dickler, Gerry: “rights”/Book 11/2/88 (Folder Item 410, Box 10)
  - Dickler, Gerry: SECY., Cap Cities 7/28/86 (Folder Item 411, Box 10)
  - Doerfler, Ron (Folder Item 412, Box 10)
  - Doerfler, Ron: 6/29/92 (Folder Item 413, Box 10)
  - Doerfler, Ron: Chief finance officer- CCC 3/1/90 (Folder Item 414, Box 10)
  - Doerfler, Ron: Chief finance ABC 12/14/90 (Folder Item 415, Box 10)
  - Dougherty, Joseph: President CCC Inc Broadcast Division NY 7/18/85 (Folder Item 416, Box 10)
  - Dougherty, Joseph: 5/17/90 (1 of 2) (Folder Item 417, Box 10)
  - Dougherty, Joseph: 5/17/90 (2 of 2) (Folder Item 418, Box 10)
  - Duncan, Dale: editor, Wilkes-Barre Times-Herald 6/86 (Folder Item 419, Box 10)
  - Edwards, Marc: KFSN Fresno 7/25/88 (Folder Item 420, Box 10)
  - Fairchild, John: 2/28/90 (Folder Item 421, Box 10)
  - Fletcher, Floyd: WTVD 7/24/85 (Folder Item 422, Box 10)
  - Fletcher, Floyd: WTVD Durham 7/26/85 (1 of 2) (Folder Item 423, Box 10)
  - Fletcher, Floyd: WTVD Durham 7/26/85 (2 of 2) (Folder Item 424, Box 10)
  - Fisher, Jim: K.C. columnist 5/21/86 (1 of 2) (Folder Item 425, Box 10)
  - Fisher, Jim and Palmer/ Baker KC 5/21/86 (2 of 2) (Folder Item 426, Box 10)
  - Fitzgerald, Ruth: Ex. secretary of Murphy 12/14/90 (Folder Item 427, Box 10)
  - Goldman, Harry: original general manager and part owner WROW-TV and WROW radio, Albany NY (Folder Item 428, Box 10)
  - Golias, Paul: Managing Editor- Citizens Voice WBPA 6/11/86 (Folder Item 429, Box 10)
  - Greup, Ernie: Ed Wall WTVD- Durham (phone) 7/25/88 (Folder Item 430, Box 10)
  - Greup, Ernie: WTVD 7/25/85 (Folder Item 431, Box 10)
  - Greup, Ernie; Miriam Bly 7/25/85 (Folder Item 432, Box 10)
  - Griffith, Bill: M.E. Times leader 6/10/86 (Folder Item 433, Box 10)
  - Hale, Jim: publisher Kansas City Star-Times 5/20/86 (Folder Item 434, Box 10)
  - Jackson, Andy: VP, Cap Cities 7/29/86 (Folder Item 435, Box 10)
  - Jackson, Andy: VP, community relations, CCC NYC- 2/27/90 and Gerry Dickler (Folder Item 436, Box 10)
  - James, Bill: WJR general manager, Cap Cities Cable president 1969-86 (Folder Item 437, Box 10)
  - Johnson, Ken: re: KTRK 1970-85 8/12/85 (Folder Item 438, Box 10)
  - Johnson, Ken: KTRK pres/general manager 5/15/85 re: Buffalo 1961-65/Albany 1965-70 (Folder Item 439, Box 10)
  - Keller, Charles: CCC Vice president, special projects 3/13/86 (Folder Item 440, Box 10)
  - Keller, Charles: Cap Cities/ABC 11/8/90 (Folder Item 441, Box 10)
  - Kuykendall, Faires: Forth Worth Star-Telegram circulation director 1938-83 (Folder Item 442, Box 10)
  - Leighton, George: announcer WROW-WTEN-TV Albany 1950-70 (Folder Item 443, Box 10)
  - Lesko, Emil, Charley Schilling: printers and Babe Knapp 6/10/86 (Folder Item 444, Box 10)
  - Lynch, Richard: Sr. VP, Fairchild also Wilkes-Barre strike 7/29/86 (Folder Item 445, Box 10)
  - Marshall, Pluria: National Black Media Coalition 7/22/86 and Pete Hoffman: McHugh Hoffman Fairfax, Va., 7/22/86 (Folder Item 446, Box 10)
  - Marshall, Pluria: National Black Media Coalition (Folder Item 447, Box 10)
  - Masucci, Jim: re: KTRK 70-85 8/12/85 (Folder Item 448, Box 10)
  - Masucci, Jim: CCB VP Programming. KTRK- Operations Manager. Albany 1956-70 5/15/85 (Folder Item 449, Box 10)
  - Matson, Patti: 6/26/90 (Folder Item 450, Box 10)
  - McCurdy, Gene: WPHL Phil., ex WPVI-TV (Folder Item 451, Box 10)
  - McGovern, Philip: Senior VP Fairchild/Cap Cities 7/29/86 (Folder Item 452, Box 10)
  - McGuff, Joe: editor, Kansas City Star Times 5/20/86 (Folder Item 453, Box 10)
  - McIntyre, Bruce: 10/14/91 (Folder Item 454, Box 10)
  - McIntyre, Bruce: Oakland press 1/30/91 (Folder Item 455, Box 10)
  - Meek, Philip: pres publishing 12/13/90 (Folder Item 456, Box 10)
  - Meek, Philip: Fort Worth Star-Telegram 6/3/86 (Folder Item 457, Box 10)
  - Meek, Philip: Fort Worth/other 6/3/86 (Folder Item 458, Box 10)
  - Meek, Philip: pres/publishing CCC NYC 2/27/90 (Folder Item 459, Box 10)
  - Miller, Jon: operations manager, WTVD formerly WPVI (Folder Item 460, Box 10)
  - Miller, Jon: Q-101 WJDQ Meridian, Miss. Meridian Advertiser Paper commercial announcement. 30 sec. (Folder Item 461, Box 10)
  - Miller, Jon (Folder Item 462, Box 10)
  - Moore, Art: director, promotion WPVI, Philadelphia 3/14/86 (Folder Item 463, Box 10)
  - Murphy, Thomas: (Back Up) copy (Folder Item 464, Box 10)
  - Murphy, Thomas: 6/29/92 (Folder Item 465, Box 10)
  - Murphy, Thomas: 10/31/85 (Folder Item 466, Box 10)
  - Murphy, Thomas: Phoenix Jan 1985 (Folder Item 467, Box 10)
  - Murphy, Thomas: IRTS: honor 1990 (Folder Item 468, Box 10)
  - Nesbitt, Alan: pres-general manager WTVD re: WPVI-TV 1975-1986 (Folder Item 469, Box 10)
  - Nesbitt, Alan: WPVI Experiences 1988 (Folder Item 470, Box 10)
  - Nesbitt, Alan: (WKBW years) / Jim Fisher, KC Star (Folder Item 471, Box 10)
  - Newby, Charles: re: Wilkes Barre Strike 6/3/86 (Folder Item 472, Box 10)
  - Orne, Peter: pres-general manager WTNH, New Haven, Conn 1971-85 (1 of 2) (Folder Item 473, Box 10)
  - Orne, Peter: (2 of 2) (Folder Item 474, Box 10)
  - Palmer, Cruise/Bill W.W. Baker: 5/21/86 KC Star Times (Folder Item 475, Box 10)
  - Peebles, Bob: WROW, Albany, NY 1959-85 (Folder Item 476, Box 10)
  - Pengelly, Allen/Dave Ward: early KTRK (Folder Item 477, Box 10)
  - Pogan, Charles “gig”: VP Programming - cap cities, program director WTEN-TV 19__-71 (Folder Item 479, Box 10)
  - Pollack, Larry: WPVI pres- 1975-86 (Folder Item 480, Box 10)
  - Pollack, Larry: WPVI pres- 1975-86 (backup) (Folder Item 481, Box 10)
  - Potash, Warren: RAB/NY- 11/9/90 (Folder Item 482, Box 10)
  - Quello, James: FCC Commissioner 7/21/86 (Folder Item 483, Box 10)
  - Rosenbloom, Joel and Roger Wallenburg, Wilmer, Cutler, and Pirckering: Cap Cities FCC attorneys, Wash. 7/23/86 (Folder Item 484, Box 10)
  - Rosenblum, Marty: Sr. VP, Fairchild (40 yr employee) 7/29/86 (Folder Item 485, Box 10)
  - Schiffman, Ben: financial officer Kansas Star-Times, retired (Folder Item 486, Box 10)
  - Schiffman, Ben: KC (backup) (Folder Item 487, Box 10)
  - Schrutt, Norm: 10/24/91 (Folder Item 488, Box 10)
  - Schrutt, Norm: Phone/Atlanta: 1/2/91 (Folder Item 489, Box 10)
  - Sias, John: pres CCC/ABC 3/12/80 (Folder Item 490, Box 10)
  - Sias, John: pres ABC-TV net 12/13/90 (Folder Item 491, Box 10)
  - Somerset, Joseph: ex VP radio Cap Cities 1974 (Folder Item 492, Box 10)
  - Sullivan, Lil: receptionist 1952-77 WTNH and D. Carmen Iannucci, chief engineer 1951-83 WTNH (Folder Item 493, Box 10)
  - Tinsley, Jack: exec ed. Fort Worth Star-Telegram 6/2/86 (Folder Item 494, Box 10)
  - Udzilla, Ted and Jane (Folder Item 495, Box 10)
  - Udzilla, Ted and Joe Schocklee: 6/10/86 (Folder Item 496, Box 10)
  - Vartigan, Ralph: announcer WTEN-TV Albany 1953-70 (Folder Item 497, Box 10)
  - Walbridge, Bill: KTRK& Cap Cities Corporate 7/10/85 (Folder Item 498, Box 10)
  - Watlach, Bob: pre-press manager T-L 6/10/86 (Folder Item 499, Box 10)
  - Wienstein, Irv: anchor WKBW TV 1964-85 (Folder Item 500, Box 10)
  - Wilkes Barre Strike: Readings, news stories, documents, 1 of 2 (Folder Item 501, Box 10)
  - Wilkes Barre Strike: Readings, news stories, documents, 2 of 2 (Folder Item 502, Box 10)
  - WROW/WTEN reunion: 6/3/94 / State Museum Vartigan/Collins Hawver (Folder Item 503, Box 10)
  - WTVD: 1) Peggy Mann 2) Marie Brown 3) Ervin Hester 4) Miriam Bly 7/25/85 (Folder Item 504, Box 10)
  - Zenick, Gerald: Associate ME 1968-present: Wilkes Barre Fort Worth Star- Telegram Strike 6/2/86 (Folder Item 505, Box 10)
- 16. Capital Cities/ABC: the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits, 16; 11 506 - 531
  Series contains early revisions of chapters one through 20, the preface, epilogue, appendices, cover and index of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986.
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Preface (Folder 506, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 1 (Folder 507, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 2 (Folder 508, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 3 (Folder 509, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 4 (Folder 510, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 5 (Folder 511, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 6 (Folder 512, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 7 (Folder 513, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 8 (Folder 514, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 9 (Folder 515, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 10 (Folder 516, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 11 (Folder 517, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 12 (Folder 518, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 13 (Folder 519, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 14 (Folder 520, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 15 (Folder 521, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 16 (Folder 522, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 17 (Folder 523, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 18 (Folder 524, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 19 (Folder 525, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Chapter 20 (Folder 526, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Epilogue (Folder 527, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Appendices (Folder 528, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Cover (Folder 529, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Index: All (Folder 530, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Edits - Index: post (Folder 531, Box 11)
- 17. Capital Cities/ABC: the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions, Suggestions and Correspondence, 17; 11 532 - 551
  Series contains editorial questions and suggestions regarding the content of chapters 2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, and 20 of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986.
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 2 (Folder 532, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 3 (Folder 533, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 5 (Folder 534, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 6 (Folder 535, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 7 (Folder 536, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 8 (Folder 537, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 9 (Folder 538, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 10 (Folder 539, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 11 (Folder 540, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 12 (Folder 541, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 13 (Folder 542, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 14 (Folder 543, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 15 (Folder 544, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 16 (Folder 545, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 17 (Folder 546, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 18 (Folder 547, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Chapter 20 (Folder 548, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Questions - Miscellaneous (Folder 549, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Suggestions and Correspondence- Patti Matson and Roann Rubin (1 of 2) (Folder 550, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Suggestions and Correspondence- Patti Matson and Roann Rubin (2 of 2) (Folder 551, Box 11)
- 18. Drafts and rewrites of Chapters 1-10 and chapter 18 of Capital Cities/ABC: The Early Years: 1954-1986, 18; 11 552 - 566
  Sereis contains assignment of copyright, published book and revisions of chapter 1-10 and chapter 18 of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 in response to earlier editorial remarks (refer to series 17).
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 1 (Folder 552, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 2 554- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 3 555- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 4 556- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 5 557- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 6 558- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 7 559- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 9 560- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 10 561- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 11 562- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 original Chapter 18 563- Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 18 (1 of 2) (Folder 553, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 rewrites Chapter 18 (2 of 2) (Folder 564, Box 11)
  - Assignment of Copyright (Folder 565, Box 11)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Published Book (Folder 566, Box 11)
- 19. Miscellany, 1953 - 1983; 19; 12 567 - 586
  Series contains miscellaneous documents, newspaper articles, pamphlets and items relating to the Walt Hawver Collection.
  - Front Page, Albany Times-Union, Nov. 23, 1963 re: JFK assassination (see flat box 12A) (Folder 567, Box 12)
  - Freedom of Information (Folder 568, Box 12)
  - Search Warrants in the Newsroom (Folder 569, Box 12)
  - Televised Executions (Folder 570, Box 12)
  - Cameras in the Courtroom (Folder 571, Box 12)
  - The FCC and Commercials (Folder 572, Box 12)
  - Disaster Coverage (Folder 573, Box 12)
  - “Boys for Sale” (Folder 574, Box 12)
  - SDX Columns on Journalism Education, Communications Ethics and Covering Political Conventions (Folder 575, Box 12)
  - Albany Knickerbocker News Poll re: Walt Hawver’s Newspaper column (Folder 576, Box 12)
  - Commentaries regarding 10 attempted prison escape and kidnapping of prison personnel at Huntsville, Texas (Folder 577, Box 12)
  - Letter to wife of Charles “Gig” Pogan, CCB leader (Folder 578, Box 12)
  - Hurricane Alicia: 1983 (Folder 579, Box 12)
  - First Amendment: Sigma Delta Chi (Folder 580, Box 12)
  - ABC Production Handbook: 1978 (Folder 581, Box 12)
  - CBS News Policy Handbook (Folder 582, Box 12)
  - Merger of ABC and United Paramount Theatres Feb. 9, 1953 (Folder 583, Box 12)
  - Miscellany (1 of 3) (Folder 584, Box 12)
  - Miscellany (2 of 3) (Folder 585, Box 12)
  - Miscellany (3 of 3) (Folder 586, Box 12)